Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Photographs, Part I: Negatives PHOTOS.023
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series I. Negatives, Bulk, 1940-1959; 1938-1969 (bulk 1940s-1950s)
  - Subseries I:D - Meetings and Events - 1938-1969
    - District 65 - Medical Plan: Rank and File Committee; Rank and FIle Members Work with Doctors; Registration; Registration - Roberta Carrington of Times-Columbia; Registration Committees Meet; Sick Visiting Committee of Brooklyn; Upper Manhattan Group Center Dedication; Kings Highway Committee Dance, Aug 9, 1956; Jul 8, 1957; May 26, 1960; Feb 24, 1954; Nov 1, 1953; Jun 18, 1954 (Negative 20360 - 20361; 14231 - 14239; 10617; 17200; 15264;16065 - 16068; 18175; 12548; 11931 - 11938; 13145 - 13151)
    - District 65 - Membership Meetings: Project; Uptown, Feb 27, 1941; Sep 9, 1941; Apr 29, 1941; 1951; Feb 1942 (Negative 568 - 575; 755; 669 - 670; 7521 - 7525; 985)
    - District 65 - Mourning for Kennedy on Marquee and Over Elevators at 13 Astor Place, Dec 1963 (Negative 22812 - 22815)
    - District 65 - Optometrist, 1961 (Negative 19553)
    - District 65 - Pension Plan: Agreement by Department Store Managements; Forum; Ciminera of Corrugated Retires, May 7, 1956; Mar 3, 1949; Jan 4, 1951 (Negative 14982; 4940; 7450 - 7452)
    - District 65 - Pharmacy: 10th Anniversary; District 65 House Vitamins; Grand Opening of Union Pharmacy; Self-Service, Apr 5, 1962; Sep 28, 1953; Oct 3, 1957; Apr 12, 1952; Apr 5, 1961 (Negative 20040 - 20043; 11748; 16268 - 16269; 8671 - 8673; 18730 - 18731)
    - District 65 - Retired Members: Jack Paley Meeting with Retiring Members, Apr 3, 1951 (Negative 7710)
    - District 65 - Retirement Plan: 6th Anniversary Celebration; Retirement Plan Committee; Retirement Plan First Applicants, May 8, 1956; Sep 19, 1951; Jan 1950 (Negative 14983 - 14990; 7946; 6153 - 6154)
    - District 65 - Security Plan: Employees Balloting; Security Plan Book for Store Workers Illustrated by Barbara Fitzgerald; Security Plan Booklets; Security Plan Committee Meetings; Forum, Jul 1949; Dec 20, 1947; Feb 28, 1956; Mar 10, 1953; Aug 21, 1956; Mar 31, 1959; 1951 (Negative 5331 - 5332; 3450; 14657; 10285; 15293; 17197; 8043 - 8044; 5075; 4873)
    - District 65 - Security Plan: Harlem Hospital; Insurance Payment [to Doswell]; Security Plan Lawyer Wins Overtime Check; Security Plan Office; Trustees Luncheon in New Cafeteria; Trustees Visit Plan Office, Apr 24, 1949; Feb 12, 1949; Dec 1948; Dec 22, 1949; Sep 30, 1948; Mar 26, 1953; Mar 3, 1949; May 1964 (Negative 4749; 28663 - 28663; 4530; 10547; 4926 - 4937; 23189 - 23190)
    - District 65 - Security Plan: Security Plan Visit of Mrs. Ray Parker and Children; A. Cohen - Physical Exam Volunteers; Elsa Hoerup Jewish Memorial Hospital, Aug 1968; Nov 1949; Apr 24, 1949 (Negative 24696 - 24700; 5740 - 5741; 5082)
    - District 65 - Service Committee: Shapiro Case, Feb 1942; Jul 1942 (Negative 973; 1221 - 1222)
    - District 65 - Services: Finance Department, Information Booth, Stockroom, Teller's Window, Aug 14, 1941 (Negative 716 - 720)
    - District 65 - Seventh Annual (Dance Comittee) [00-00-40?], 1940 (Negative 337)
    - District 65 - Socials Committee, Mar 27, 1941 (Negative 595)
    - District 65 - Softball: Meeting; Gaylord vs. Republic, Mar 31, 1948; Mar 5, 1941; May 7, 1949 (Negative 3582; 60; 5135 - 5137)
    - District 65 - Song Book Committee: with Earl Robinson, Dec 1939 (Negative 29698 - 29699)
    - District 65 - Spanish Affairs Committee: Subcommittee on Civil Rights and Union Leadership; Emergency Meeting; Meetings; Preparing Copy for Spanish Page; Spanish Affairs Fiesta Committee, Nov 1949; Apr 1, 1959; Oct 15, 1959; Jun 12, 1942; Feb 7, 1948; Mar 30, 1950; Feb 19, 1953; Jul 28, 1953; Oct 29, 1953; Jun 24, 1954; Sep 16, 1954; Sep 30, 1954; Apr 19, 1956; Mar 24, 1960 (Negative 5762 - 5765; 17201; 17687; 1170; 3522; 6388; 10182; 11420; 11889; 13183; 13384; 13495 - 13496; 14811;18005 - 18006; 16441)
    - District 65 - Spanish Affairs Committee: Labor Advisory Committee; Exhibit Photographs of Hiring Hall, Staff and Retired Members; Social; Spanish Fiesta Tix Sale, Mar 20, 1958; Aug 24, 1956; Aug 12, 1949; Nov 20, 1952; Jul 21, 1954; Feb 14, 1961; Nov 1949; Apr 28, 1950; Apr 6, 1956; Nov 1, 1954; Sep 14, 1949; Apr 1, 1948 (Negative 15295 - 15296; 5416 - 5419; 9971; 13245; 18673; 5815 - 5816; 6569; 14771; 13476 - 13483; 5511 - 5519; 3584)
    - District 65 - Sports: Sports Committee; Sports Council, Mar 3, 1942; 1949 (Negative 1008; 5360 - 5361)
    - District 65 - Staff: African Students, Aug 6, 1962 (Negative 20307 - 20318)
    - District 65 - Staff: Meeting; Meeting Hears Professor Robert Ferguson of Cornell on Economic Recession [Includes Shots with Robinson, Livingston, Reverby]; Staff Show Saturday Nightclub; Welcome Home, Oct 23, 1954; May 27, 1958; Jan 7, 1950; Apr 7, 1956; May 5, 1946 (Negative 13437 - 13448; 16578 - 16579; 6060 - 6062; 26003 - 26009; 14772; 2623 - 2624)
    - District 65 - Supply Committee, Oct 7, 1940 (Negative 257)
    - District 65 - Suspended Meeting, Oct 22, 1942 (Negative 1291 - 1292)
    - District 65 - T.V.: Antenna Broken by the Wind, Jan 6, 1958 (Negative 17028)
    - District 65 - Tax Committee: Advisory Committee; Committee, Feb 2, 1953; Jan 29, 1951 (Negative 9782; 7514)
    - District 65 - Theatre Group: Singing at January General Council Meeting, Jan 1969 (Negative 25801 - 25805)
    - District 65 - Trial Committee, Sep 25, 1940 (Negative 29674)
    - District 65 - Union Book, Apr 5, 1962 (Negative 20044 - 20045)
    - District 65 - Union Voice Newspaper: Basketball Physicals; Union Voice Chorus; Discount Book; Office and Sign, Oct 31, 1950; Feb 19, 1951; May 15, 1948; Mar 18, 1948 (Negative 7291 - 7292; 7601; 4149; 3567)
    - District 65 - Upholstery Committee, Oct 31, 1940 (Negative 389)
    - District 65 - Visitors: Judy (?) Baldinger's Class Tour District 65; Lancaster [Pennsylvania Local] Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America (D.P.O.W.A.) Visits District 65; Latin-American Delegation Tours District 65; Mexican Students Tour District 65 Headquarters; Milton C. Johnson Workers Touring District 65 Building; Old Dutch - Baker Brand Rank and File Committee, Oct 19, 1960; Apr 14, 1951; Jul 24, 1953; May 1, 1954; Aug 10, 1961; Jul 27, 1954; Oct 6, 1952; Feb 24, 1958; Jun 10, 1959; Jul 1963; Mar 24, 1959; May 4, 1956; Apr 12, 1957; Jan 7, 1960; 1950; Oct 21, 1955 (Negative 18302; 7731 - 7732; 11384 - 11385; 13715 - 13718; 19179 - 19181; 13265; 9510 - 9512; 16375 - 16383; 17384 - 17387; 22441 - 22446; 17195; 14968; 15873 - 15874; 17799; 6346 - 6347; 14408; 23265 - 23272)
    - District 65 - Visitors: Philadelphia Visitors at Consumer Service; Eleanor Roosevelt Visits District 65 Center; Retail Wholesale Department Store Employees Union (RWDSU) General Council Members Touring District 65; Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee (S.N.C.C.) Visitors; Stern-Paramus Members Visit District 65 Center; Students of Cornell, New York State School of Industrial Relations Visit District 65; Students Visit District 65 Center; Youth Board of New York City Visits District 65; Miners at Local 65; Delegation of Girl Scouts Tour 65; Hiroshima and Nagasaki Survivors Visit General Council; Visitors from Rochelle, Illinois; Visit by Charleston Delegation (visit to Garment Center); To District 65 Headquarters from Suffolk Virginia Local 26; NYU Students Touring District 65; A.F.L.-C.I.O. Convention Delegates Tour and Dine At District 65 Center; Air Masters Visit to 13 Astor Place; Australian Member of Parliament Visits District 65, Jun 3, 1964; Mar 10, 1951; Jul 3, 1952; Aug 26, 1953; Oct 8, 1952; Dec 6, 1955; Jun 1963; Apr 12, 1955; Jul 8, 1955; Jul 7, 1954; Oct 23, 1959; May 1963; Feb 19, 1957; Jun 14, 1955; May 18, 1955; Sep 20, 1955 (Negative 7639 - 7643; 9172 - 9180; 11606; 9525 - 9526; 14486 - 14488; 21882 - 21887; 14008 - 14012; 14250; 13204 - 13205; 17702; 21719 - 21720; 15761; 14166 - 14172)
    - District 65 - Visitors: Austrian Delegation; Charleston South Carolina Local 15 Member Ethel Simmons Visits District 65; Chilean Visitors Tour District 65; Cosmair Workers Visit, 13 Astor Place; FeliciaDe Gautier Rincon, Mayor of San Juan, Puerto Rico, Visits District 65 Center [Cleveland Robinson]; Delegation from Cuba; Delegation From Honduras; Delegation From Iceland; European Trade Unionists Tour District 65 Center; French Trade Unionist Pierre Grandt Visits District 65 Center; German Union Delegation Tours District 65; Hunter College Students' Visits to District 65; International Longshoren and Warehouse Union (ILWU) Visitors at District 65 Retirement Plan; Israel Barzilar, Israeli Minister of Health, Uses District 65 Optical Services [David Livingston]; Tour of District 65 Center by Hunter College Students; Reverends Tour 65; Rev. T Graham and Family from Cinncinnati; British Labour Leaders, Mar 14, 1958; Sep 9, 1958; Aug 14, 1952; Nov 24, 1959; Aug 6, 1958; Nov 27, 1957; 1951; May 22, 1958; Oct 21, 1946; Aug 3, 1954; Aug 21, 1968; Dec 24, 1943 (Negative 14123 - 14128; 14346 - 14349; 16429 - 16431; 16673; 9324 - 9325; 17741; 16635; 16278 - 16279; 8248 - 3250; 1District 6570; 2880; 13266 - 13268; 24837 - 24840; 1588)
    - District 65 - Voter Registration, Aug-Sep, 1964 (Negative 23461 - 23469)
    - District 65 - Wage Policy Committee Meeting; Subcommittee, Jul 25, 1951; Jul 31, 1951 (Negative 7791 - 7793; 7827)
    - District 65 - Welfare: Welfare Committee Meeting; Welfare Service, Oct 28, 1941; Mar 2, 1950 (Negative 800; 6373)
    - District 65 - Women's Affairs Committee: Cosmetic Show; UNICEF Luncheon; Petitioning; Conference; Conference Committee, Jul 1960; Jan 1942; Jun 6, 1961; Apr 28, 1962; Dec 23, 1940; Aug 17, 1960; Dec 13, 1940; Dec 6, 1940 (Negative 18197; 946; 19024 - 19026; 20091 - 20100; 29649 - 29650; 18215; 157-159; 154 - 155)
    - District 65 - Yanks Are Not Coming Committee, undated (Negative 29697; 29706; 29706)
    - District 65 - Youth Activities Committee: Election and Dance; Meetings; Members Speak at Membership Meetings; Works on Mailing to Members, Aug 18, 1960; Apr 18, 1960; Feb 20, 1960; Mar 24, 1960; Apr 13, 1960 (Negative 18221; 18052 - 18057; 18029 - 18041; 17997 - 17998; 18042 - 18043)
    - District 65 - Alumni: Committee Classes, Aug 25, 1955; Aug 12, 1954 (Negative 14318; 13304)
    - District 65- Laws and Records Committee (Jack Brust, Rose Roth, Abe Hendler, Sid Kraus), Jan 2, 1941 (Negative 275)
    - Dixie Mail Order, May 1, 1942 (Negative 3255)
    - Donnelly Metal Co.: Newly-Organized Shop, Sep 9, 1957 (Negative 16099)
    - Do-Nut Meetings; Do-Nut Ratification, Oct 27, 1952; Mar 6, 1952 (Negative 9855 - 9856; 8532)
    - Doral Textile: Newly-Organized, Sep 8, 1958 (Negative 16674)
    - Dorothy Curtain Shop: Newly-Organized, Oct 25, 1960 (Negative 18470 - 18471)
    - Dorothy Fabrics: Newly-Organized shop, Mar 8, 1955 (Negative 13951)
    - Dorset Foods: Ratification; Meetings, Feb 28, 1942; Oct 1942; Feb 28, 1942 (Negative 30167 - 30168; 1306; 987)
    - Doubleday Book Committee, Jun 30, 1930 (Negative 11186)
    - Downtown: Council Group; General Council; Meeting; Membership Meeting; Secretaries, Aug 13, 1952; Sep 9, 1952; Feb 13, 1941; Mar 23, 1942; Jun 18, 1942 (Negative 9322; 9396; 536 - 537; 1046 - 1048; 1046 - 1048; 1172)
    - DPOWA Officers, Osman-Henderson-Durkin, Oct 3, 1950 (Negative 7134 - 7136)
    - Drapon Shop, Feb 10, 1961; Apr 11, 1961 (Negative 18670; 18762 - 18763)
    - Dresden Workers Sworn in, Oct 30, 1947 (Negative 3172)
    - Drug Local 1199: Negro History Celebration; Executive Board; Installation; Workers Contract Ratification Hotel Claridge, Feb 28, 1960; Oct 5, 1961; Apr 16, 1952; Mar 29, 1950 (Negative 17976 - 17986; 19331; 8724 - 8727; 6471)
    - Dry Goods Association, Sep 1942 (Negative 1270 - 1271)
    - Dry Goods: Banquet Committee; Bonus Mobilization; Contract Ratification; Crew 1; Crew Election; Crew Elections; 21 Broadway, Sussman, Luba; Executive Board; Local Executive Board; Meeting; Members Voting For New Contract; Membership Meeting; Negotiating Committee; Negotiations, Jan 27, 1954; Jan 26, 1948; Dec 19, 1951; Jan 7, 1957; Feb 7, 1956; Feb 10, 1954; Feb 15, 1953; Jan 27, 1955; May 3, 1956; Sep 18, 1956; Dec 3, 1951; undated; Nov 23, 1959; Feb 22, 1961; Jan 15, 1953; Aug 25, 1955; Nov 12, 1951; Nov 26, 1956 (Negative 12373; 3503 - 3504; 8253 - 8254; 15615; 14619; 12437; 9830 - 9830; 13749; 14970; 15344; 8329; 24379 - 24393; 17739 - 17740; 18682 - 18684; 9708 - 9709)
    - Dry Goods (con't): United Jewish Appeal (UJA) (JJ Goldstein); Outside Salesmen; Shop Meeting; Excuse Committee; Discusses Mundt Bill; Shops Meet on Negotiations; Special Executive Board Meetings; Special Membership Meeting; Stipulations (J. Tillem - F. Lichtblau, F. Quinn), Mar 20, 1957; Jun 22, 1944; Sep 22, 1953; Oct 1962; Mar 5, 1946; May 4, 1948; May 5, 1955; Dec 11, 1957; Jan 24, 1957; Aug 22, 1950; Jul 31, 1947 (Negative 14319 - 14320; 8170; 15557; 15850; 1839; 11698; 20574 - 20575; 2522; 4119; 14056 - 14057; 16291; 15638; 7064; 3089)
    - Dues Inspection, Oct 29, 1966; Mar 21, 1956 (Negative 24324 - 24332; 14722)
    - Dues Payment Crowd, Jan 10, 1942 (Negative 899)
    - Dunhill Meeting; Shop, Sep 8, 1955; Oct 26, 1955 (Negative 14336; 14417)
    - E. J. Willis - Fire At, 1952 (Negative 8740 - 8751)
    - E-1 [East Side Section 1]: Meeting; Organizer [see also 08-19-43]; Stewards; Stewards Meetings; Swearing in New Members, Apr 1, 1940; Aug 31, 1943; Feb 5, 1942; Aug 11, 1941; Jul 29, 1942 (Negative 451; 962)
    - E-2 [East Side Section 2]: Section Stewards; Stewards, Jan 22, 1941; Feb 4, 1942 (Negative 454; 967; 582; 961)
    - E-3 [East Side Section 3]: Section Stewards, Jan 23, 1941; Feb 5, 1942; Mar 3, 1941; Feb 4, 1942 (Negative 454; 967; 582; 961)
    - E-6 [East Side Section 6]: Chairman Candidates; Stewards, Dec 10, 1943; Feb 5, 1942 (Negative 1587; 969)
    - Eagle Straw Election, Apr 29, 1941 (Negative 667 - 668)
    - Eaglo: Election; Meeting; Shop Taking Oath of Membership; Workers, Jun 30, 1961; Jul 27, 1961; Jun 15, 1961; Nov 25, 1961 (Negative 19126; 19150 - 19151; 19075 - 19076; 19533)
    - East Harlem Committee Meeting, Apr 6, 1954 (Negative 12772)
    - East Side Community Meeting, Jan 18, 1944 (Negative 1606 - 1607)
    - East Side Staff, Mar 10, 1940 (Negative 29632)
    - Eastern Camera Shop Meeting, Apr 16, 1962 (Negative 20075 - 20078)
    - Eckstein Shop, Aug 22, 1944 (Negative 1930)
    - Egg Sale at Local 2, Dec 17, 1947 (Negative 3448)
    - Einson - Freeman: Contract Ratification; Shop Meetings, 1952; Jul 2, 1953; Nov 18, 1953 (Negative 8457; 11223 - 11224; 12028)
    - Elections Committee, Jan 12, 1940; Nov 26, 1940; Dec 2, 1953; Jan 5, 1954; Apr 3, 1956; Sep 30, 1957; Nov 4, 1957; Jun 16, 1958; Sep 18, 1958; Jun 14, 1960 (Negative 12105; 12272; 14763; 16127; 16256; 16601; 16683; 18191; 29664; 29689 - 29690)
    - Elections for District 65 Officers 1948, Jun 15, 1948 (Negative 4313 - 4317)
    - Elections: Candidates; Tabulation; Of District 65 Officers; Of Stewards Miles Shoes; Of Stewards, Local 65 [1/50]; Run-Off Toy and Gift; of Union Officers - Mobile Unit at Bloomingdale Warehouse; 1942; 06/12th and 18th/56; At Union Headquarters; Local 1250 B. Loesers, Jan 1940; Jan 6, 1941; Jan 13, 1941; Jan 5, 1942; Jan 10, 1942; Apr 24, 1944; Jun 12, 1946; Jan 1950; Apr 21, 1950; Jun 11, 1952; May 7, 1953; Jun 1956; Oct 15, 1958; May 8, 1962; Jun 4, 1962; Sep 26, 1962 (Negative 335-336; 349 -351; 885; 888-889; 902 -904; 2705-2707; 6055-6056; 6546 – 6550; 9041 - 9058; 9065-9066; 10730; 15187-15199; 16798 -16800; 20221-20229; 20109 -20122; 20540-20543)
    - Elgin Knit, Nov 13, 1952; Nov 25, 1952 (Negative 9940; 10000)
    - Emblem Contest Entries Ben Berman, 1950 (Negative 6435)
    - Emergency General Council Meeting, 1952 (Negative 8623 - 8633)
    - Emergency Meeting: Joe Curran, Sol Mils; C.I.O.-A.F.L. Representatives at Commodore Hotel, Aug 13, 1940; Oct 15, 1953 (Negative 149 - 152; 11818 - 11825)
    - Empire Corrugated Meeting, Sep 24, 1957 (Negative 16125)
    - Empire Findings, Jul 17, 1942 (Negative 1203)
    - Empire Textile Election, Jan 23, 1956 (Negative 14576)
    - Enrich: Committee: Shop Meetings; Ratification and Committee, Dec 14, 1940; Nov 19, 1940; Dec 19, 1940; Aug 20, 1942; Dec 26, 1940; Sep 2, 1941; Jan 26, 1954 (Negative 29652; 332; 29646 - 29647; 1237; 29644; 740; 12345)
    - Entertainment Midtown Area Membership Meeting, Jul 1949 (Negative 5326 - 5329)
    - Ernest Slide Co. Stoppage: David Livingston at Shop Meeting, May 17, 1946 (Negative 2632)
    - Essex Nassau Meeting, undated (Negative 24715 - 24718)
    - Ever Ready Label Shop: Assists Newly-Organized Machinists in Jersey City; Workers Ratify 1957 Reopener; Negotiating Committee; Ratifies 1954 Contract, undated; Mar 30, 1957; Mar 5, 1956; Apr 6, 1954 (Negative 29985; 15858; 16414; 12771)
    - Everlast Priniting: Labor Unity Party; Conference; Strike Meeting, Sep 26, 1961; Jan 22, 1951; Aug 10, 1961; May 25, 1962 (Negative 19312 - 19313; 7502 - 7503; 19183; 20181 - 20186)
    - Everlite Mfg. Co.: Newly-Organized, Jun 25, 1958 (Negative 16621)
    - Executive Board (1938-39) (Negative 29673)
    - Executive Board (Lumber), Sep 17, 1953 (Negative 11671 - 11672)
    - Executive Board Meeting, Apr 7, 1941 (Negative 628)
    - Executive Board Meetings on Wages, Sep 14, 1950 (Negative 7107 - 7109)
    - Executive Boards: Dry Goods,Hardware, Food and Tobacco, Drug, Needle Processing, Paper Products, May 16, 1946 (Negative 2626 - 2630)
    - Express Cont[ainer?] (Ratification), Feb 8, 1941 (Negative 526)
    - F and K [Yarn] Ratification, Jan 1942 (Negative 960)
    - Famous Knit Mobilization, Jul 11, 1946 (Negative 2723 - 2724)
    - Farnow Varnish, Apr 11, 1957 (Negative 15866)
    - Father Duffy at Bronx Area Meeting, Sep 13, 1949 (Negative 5496 - 5497)
    - Federal Adhesives Contract Ratification, Mar 3, 1952 (Negative 8521 - 8521)
    - Felsway Shoe Shop Meeting, Jan 25, 1954 (Negative 12335)
    - Fight for VFT at P. Rothman, May 9, 1946 (Negative 2625)
    - Filling Food Bags for Newark Riot Victims also Distribution, 1967 (Negative 25150 - 25158)
    - Fine Wool Shop in Finance Getting Union Books, 1968 (Negative 24999 - 25000)
    - First African-American Salesman in Millinery Market at Schuman and Stein- Starline Bag, Dec 11, 1958 (Negative 16965 - 16966)
    - First Group Insurance Payment Recipient, Anna Disner, Nov 2, 1945 (Negative 2383)
    - First Local 830 Group Insurance Check, Jan 24, 1946 (Negative 2474)
    - First Recreation Director's Meeting, Oct 2, 1945 (Negative 2317)
    - Fischer and White Plains Duplicating: Newly-Organized Workers, Nov 1962 (Negative 21021)
    - Fischer Distributers Shop, 1952 (Negative 9204)
    - Fisher - Stevens: Meetings; 1955 Pact Signed By 65 and Management; Committees; Executive Board; Newly-Organized Direct Mail Shop, Mar 1, 1955; Feb 9, 1955; Sep 22, 1955; Sep 16, 1954; Nov 27, 1956; Dec 13, 1955; Sep 21, 1953; Sep 14, 1953 (Negative 13851 - 13853; 13820; 14356 - 14358; 13385; 15558; 14510; 11686 - 11688; 11670)
    - Fleck Broiler Ratification [probably 11/49], Nov 1949 (Negative 5772)
    - Florn [?] Company Organization, Sep 5, 1961 (Negative 19240 - 19241)
    - Flu Injections Given to Staff 65ers, Oct 17, 1957 (Negative 16159 - 16160)
    - Food and Drug Control to Phelps Dodge, May 16, 1946 (Negative 2634)
    - Food and Drug Membership Meeting, Aug 10, 1943 (Negative 1511)
    - Food and Metal Processing Local Officers in Local with Organizer Bellenare, Nov 8, 1954 (Negative 13502)
    - Food Packages for Italy, 1952 (Negative 8786)
    - Food: Division Stewards; Executive Board; Local Spanish Membership Meeting; Membership; Spanish Food Membership; Food for U.E. Strikers, Jan 27, 1954; Jul 15, 1952; Jan 31, 1941; Aug 17, 1954; Oct 7, 1953; Dec 16, 1953; Oct 21, 1954
    - Footwear Division: Contract Ratification; Election; Membership Meetings; Executive Board; Good Standing Plaque; Ratification of Demand; Mobilizes at War Labor Board; Ratifies 1946 Contract, Mar 12, 1952; Sep 27, 1943; Aug 16, 1943; May 15, 1946; May 16, 1945; Aug 5, 1953; Jun 14, 1944; Nov 15, 1944; Feb 9, 1949; Jun 25, 1945; Apr 30, 1946 (Negative 8549; 1535 - 1537; 1496; 29529; 2165; 11450; 1823; 1999 - 2002; 4867; 2199 - 2200; 2620)
    - Fourth Area Organizes, Jan 21, 1949 (Negative 4846)
    - Fourth Avenue Membership Meeting, Feb 27, 1952 (Negative 8514 - 8516)
    - Frank Bros., Jul 24, 1942 (Negative 1218)
    - Frank Brown: Brown Team Organization Meeting; National Container Statements; Irma Brown's Last Day of Work Before Maternity Leave; Frank Brown of District 65 Headquarters Elevator Operator Retires; Frank Brown's Team, Cleveland Robinson Addressing General Council, Mar 1963; Aug 10, 1943; May 14, 1954; Sep 28, 1958; 1967 (Negative 21277; 29708; 12909; 16793 - 16794; 24936 - 24941)
    - Frank Brown Co. Reunion, Nov 2, 1945 (Negative 2384 - 2385)
    - Frank D. Britz (?) Co Committee Negotiating with Attorney F. Lewis Gross and J. Rappaport Loc. of A. King, Apr 1967 (Negative 24515)
    - Freeman Knit: Newly-Organized, Aug 19, 1957 (Negative 16101)
    - Friends of 65 Joining [Meeting; People Signing Up], Mar 19, 1942 (Negative 1043 - 1044)
    - Frisch Paint Co. Meeting, Feb 3, 1954 (Negative 12408)
    - Froehlich and Co.: Arbitration; Workers - Head Shots; Ratification, Oct 13, 1942; Jan 1943; Sep 26, 1941 (Negative 1276 - 1277; 1357 - 1360; 775)
    - Frost Shop Meeting, Jun 1950 (Negative 6946)
    - Fuld and Co. Ratification, Mar 31, 1943 (Negative 1402)
    - Funeral of Steward Luisa Diaz, Sep 6, 1968 (Negative 29907 - 29921)
    - Furlanger Shop Taking Oath of Membership, Apr 29, 1952 (Negative 8723)
    - Furniture Workers Union, Feb 19, 1947 (Negative 29548 - 29549)
    - G. E.: Meeting; Ratifies Contract; Warehouse, Feb 26, 1946; Apr 18, 1946; Apr 17, 1946 (Negative 2515; 2591; 2607 - 2608)
    - Garfield News: Meeting; Strike Meeting, Jan 26, 1951; Mar 5, 1952; Jun 30, 1953; Mar 9, 1955; Nov 24, 1954; Feb 25, 1953 (Negative 7511; 8528 - 8529; 11185; 13956; 13594; 10246)
    - Garment Area: Meeting; Membership Meeting at Manhattan Center; Rank and File Organizing Committee; Swearing-In of New Members, Mar 19, 1952; Jun 21, 1955; Aug 6, 1956; Sep 18, 1950 (Negative 8573 - 8574; 14211 - 14227; 15242 - 15243; 7114)
    - Garment Center: [Meeting of] National Association of Women and Children's Apparel Salesman (NAWCAS) Manhattan Center; Dress Rehearsal; Expirations; Locals Meet for Joint Organizing Campaign; Meeting - Manhattan Center; Members Meet on Organizing Assignments; Organizing Committee; Moment Of Silence Garment Center Local For Ray Parker, Apr 22, 1968; Apr 29, 1965; Apr 21, 1962; Mar 11, 1959; Apr 14, 1965; Oct 5, 1959; Oct 20, 1955; Aug 1967 (Negative 25362 - 25368; 23971 - 23986; 20079; 17171; 23987 - 24000; 17654 - 17655; 14411; 25170)
    - Garment Crew: Crew 13 Ind. Quilt, Trade; Crew 1; Crew #3 Election, Feb 10, 1954; Jan 7, 1954; Jan 23, 1956 (Negative 12438; 12284; 14575)
    - Garment Executive Board, Aug 20, 1956 (Negative 15265)
    - Garment Industries Locals Executive Boards, Jun 7, 1955 (Negative 14159 - 14160)
    - Garment Lace Shops, May 27, 1957 (Negative 15961)
    - Garment Members: Being Sworn-In; Meetings, Jun 18, 1957; May 19, 1955; Sep 21, 1953 (Negative 16001; 14132 - 14134; 11693)
    - Garment Strike Committee, Jan 20, 1958 (Negative 16318)
    - Garment Supply [aka Garment Supplies]: Organizing Committee; Executive Board; Meetings; Membership Meeting; Shops, Jul 11, 1944; Jul 28, 1944; May 20, 1946; Feb 15, 1956; May 12, 1943; Aug 22, 1949; Jan 12, 1953; Apr 22, 1953; May 24, 1961; Dec 3, 1961; Apr 29, 1953 (Negative 1869; 1893 - 1894; 2651; 14635; 1438; 5435; 9644; 10665 - 10666; 18958 - 18960; 19537 - 19540; 10706)
    - Garment Team Award, 1951 (Negative 7968)